Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Foreign Politics Serials TAM.765
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Foreign Politics Serials
1850-2011
1940-1989
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
TAM.765
20.6 Linear Feet in 30 manuscript boxes, 3 half manuscript boxes, 20 flat boxes, and 5 custom enclosures
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Foreign Politics Serials contains over 300 titles on politics in Europe, Canada, Asia, Latin America, Africa, and Oceania as well as international issues. The collection dates between 1850 and 2011, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1940s through 1980s. Topics include politics within countries other than the United States, issues in the Middle East and the Soviet Union in the early to mid-20th century, Palestinian independence movements, and the Cold War.
Arrangement
Serials in this collection are arranged alphabetically by title.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection combines serials relating to foreign politics drawn from two discrete groups of material held by the Tamiment Library. The first was a partially inventoried backlog of serials, received by the library through donations, subscriptions, and in archival collections. The second group consisted of around 1,700 serials, newspapers, and magazines, organized by title as an artificial collection, referred to as Periodicals.001 or Boxed Newspapers. This material was combined, inventoried, and arranged and described in subject-based categories in 2017. The accession number related to this collection is 2017.049.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to the fragile nature of certain original materials, researchers may be required to consult microfilm copies, preservation photocopies, or digital images of material in this collection.
Scope and Contents
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Foreign Politics Serials contains over 300 titles on politics in Europe, Canada, Asia, Latin America, Africa, and Oceania as well as international issues. The collection dates between 1850 and 2011, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1940s through 1980s. Topics include national and local politics mainly within European countries, issues in the Middle East and the Soviet Union in the early to mid-20th century, Palestinian independence movements, and the Cold War. The collection includes titles published in the US on these topics, as well as on international affairs, including the Cold War and the Middle East. Other topics include issues of interest to immigrant communities, in particular Eastern European immigrants in the US; the World Federalist Movement; the Vietnam War; and topics of interest to minority and opposition groups in Iran, Israel, and South America. Large runs of titles include camb16, Commonwealth, and Informations Ouvrières.
International relations.; Serials (publications); Newspapers.; Europe -- Politics and government -- 20th century.; Independence movements.; Middle East -- Politics and government.; Cold War.
- 3D: 3D, London, UK, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- 7 Days: 7 Days Publishing Co. Ltd., London, UK, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
- 70's Biweekly: 70's Biweekly, Hong Kong, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- 9th June: Peoples Front for the Liberation of the Occupied Arabian Gulf, Maalla, Yemen, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- A Coups de Baionnette: La Baionnette, Paris, France, 1915-1917 (Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49)
- A Monthly Survey of Foreign Affairs: Conservative Political Center, London, UK, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- A World to Win: World to Win, London, UK, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Abyot: Ethiopian Peoples' Revolutionary Party - Foreign Committee, Ethiopia, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ACTivist: ACT for Disarmament Coalition, Ontario, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Advance: E.L.F. Office, Damascus, Syria, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Africa News: A Weekly Digest of African Affairs: Africa News Service, Inc., Durham, NC, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- African & Colonial World: Independent Publishing Co., London, UK, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- African Youth: African Youth Movement for Liberation and Unity, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- AJME News: Americans for Justice in the Middle East, Beirut, Lebanon, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- AKEL news letter: Central Committee of the Progressive Party of the Working People, Nicosia, Cyprus, 1965-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Al Urdun: Jordan Information Bureau, Washington, DC, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Albania Report: Gamma Publishing, Inc., New York, NY, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Albania Today: Albania Today, Tirana, Albania, 1971-1982 (Box 31, Folder 1-5, Box 32, Folder 1-4)
- Albania Today Supplement: Albania Today, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Amanee: National Union of Ghanaian Students (Europe), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Annals of Public and Co-operative Economy: International Centre of Research and Information on Public and Co-operative Economy, Liege, Belgium, 1969-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18-20, Box 2, Folder 1-3, Folder 10)
- antifa forum: AFF, Toronto, Ontario, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Antifascism in Canada: antifa forum, Toronto, Ontario, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Antistase, Greece, 1968-1969 (Box Shared Tamiment 061, Folder 6)
- API-HH Newsletter and Information Bulletin: Americans for Progressive Israel Hashomer Hatzair, New York, NY, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Arauco: Pensa Latinoamericana S.A., Santiago, Chile, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Asia and Africa: Asia and Africa Today, Moscow, USSR, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Back to the Future: Heritage Editions, USA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Balkan War Report: Institute for War & Peace Reporting, London, UK, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Вестник Общества Велимира Хлебникова: Гилея, Moskva: Gilei︠a︡, New York, NY, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Behind the Crisis: United Front in Support of the Iranian People, Chicago, IL, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Beispiele: Europaische Verlagsanstalt, Frankfurt, Germany, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Bericht der Zentrale an den 4. Parteitag der SPD: Zentrale der SPD, Berlin, Germany, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Berliner Arbeiter Zeitung: Sozialistische Deutsche Arbeiterpartei, Berlin, Germany, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Black Star: Black Star Publications, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Boletin Catolico Checoslovaco: Servicio Informativo del Gobierno Checoslovaco, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Bollettino Interno: Commissione di Corrispondenza FAI, Carrara, Italy, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Breaking the Siege: Middle East Justice Network, Cambridge, MA, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Briarpatch: Briarpatch Magazine, Regina, Saskatchewan, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- British Columbia Monthly: Gerry Gilbert and Bob Amussen, Vancouver, British Columbia, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Bulletin: Interhemispheric Resource Center, Albuquerque, NM, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Bulletin: Socialist Unity Party of Germany, Paris, France, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Bulletin du Cercle Libertaire des Etudiants: Cercle Libertaire des Etudiants, Paris, France, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Bulletin of the National Front of Iran in the U.S., 1963 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Byelorussian Voice: Byelorussian-American Association, Toronto, Ontario, 1964 (Box Shared Tamiment 047, Folder 1)
- C&L (Culture & Life): Izvestia Printing, Moscow, USSR, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- C.A.D.D.Y. Bulletin: The Democracy International Committee to Aid Democratic Residents in Yugoslavia, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Cahiers D'Europe: Paris, France, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- camb16: camb16, Madrid, Spain, 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 5-6, Box 33, Folder 1-5, Box 34, Folder 1-6, Box 35, Folder 1-3)
- Canadian Democrat: the canadian democrat, Toronto, Ontario, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Candour: Candour Publishing Co., Croydon, UK, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- CCL News Letter: Caribbean Congress of Labour, Port-of-Spain, Trinidad, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- CERI-GUA: Centro Exterior de Reportes Informativos Sobre Guatemala, Managua, Nicaragua, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Charlie Hebdo: Kalachnikoff, Paris, France, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Chasqui Newsletter: Buffalo - Office of Political Prisoners and Human Rights in Chile, Buffalo, NY, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Choc: Choc, Paris, France, 1937 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Circle: The Circle 53, Port-of-Spain, Trinidad, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Civilisation Libertaire: Cahiers d'Etudes Sociologiques: Gaston Leval, Paris, France, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Class War: Class War Federation, Bristol, UK, 1990-1996 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Combat: Combat, Paris, France, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 9-10)
- Committee for a Free Grenada: Committee for a Free Grenada, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Committee to Support Middle East Liberation Newsletter: Committee to Support Middle East Liberation, New York, NY, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Commonwealth: New Democratic Party, Regina, Saskatchewan, 1977-1989 (Box 24, Folder 1-7, Box 44, Folder 7-15, Box 43, Folder 1-15, Box 42, Folder 1-16)
- Congo People's Voice: The Congo Support Committee, New York, NY, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Connexions Digest: The Connexions Digest, Toronto, Canada, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Corta: Corta, Montevideo, Uruguay, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Counter Information: Counter Information Collective, Edinburgh, Scotland, 1987-1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Cuban Affairs: Asuntos Cubanos: Cuban Committee for Democracy, Washington, DC, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Current Sweden: Swedish Institute, Stockholm, Sweden, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Daily Report Supplement: Foreign Broadcast Information Service, Moscow, USSR, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Das Blattchen: Das Blattchen, Berlin, Germany, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- de kargadoor: mog steeds een sinjaalgevoelig instituut, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
- De Soldatenkrant: De Soldatenkrant, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 16, Box 23, Folder 5)
- Defendamos la Revolucion: Secretaria de Propaganda FSLN, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Democracy Wall: Democracy Wall Editorial Committee, Hong Kong, China, Undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Democratie Nouvelle: E. Aubel, Paris, France, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Der Antifaschistische Widerstandskampfer: Zentralleitung des Komitees der Antifaschistischen Widerstandskampfer der DDR, Berlin, Germany, 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Der Deutsche Krieg Politische Flugschriften von Ornst Jacth: Deutsche Verlags-Unstalt, Berlin, Germany, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Der Funke: Der Funke, Berlin, Germany, 1933 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Der Monat: Office of Military Government in Germany, Berlin, Germany, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
- Desde Uruguay: Desde Uruguay, Montevideo, Uruguay, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Deutsche Post: Deutschen Postgewerkschaft, Frankfurt, Germany, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Development & Socioeconomic Progress: Afro-Asian Peoples' Solidarity Organization, Cairo, Egypt, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Die Aktion: Die Aktion, Paris, France, 1933 (Box Shared Tamiment 047, Folder 2)
- Die Deutsche Revolution: Dr. Otto Strasser, Germany, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 6, Folder 11)
- Die Konsumgenossenschaft: Verbandes Deutscher Wirtschaftsgenossenschaften und der GEC-Grosseinkaufsgesellschaft fur Consumvereine, Berlin, Germany, 1925-1928 (Box 9, Folder 2, Folder 8-9)
- Die Menschheit: Wiesbaden, Germany, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Die Neue Gesellschaft: Verlag Neue Gesellschaft GmbH, Bonn, Germany, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Die Neue Volkszahlungs-Zeitung: Vienna, Austria, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Die Weltbuhne: Carl v. Ossietsky, Berlin, Germany, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Documents et Actualities: Federation Democratique Internationale des Femmes, Berlin, Germany, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- East European Reporter: East European Reporter, Budapest, Hungary, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- East Express: INTAKAS, Vilnius, Lithuania, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Economic Reform Newsletter of the Committee on Monetary and Economic Reform: The Committee on Monetary and Economic Reform, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Ejercito del Ebro: Ejercito del Ebro, Spain, Undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
- El Eco de Nayarit: El Eco de Nayarit, Acaponeta, Mexico, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- En Defense de Michel Raptis (Pablo) et Sal Santen: Comites de Soutien Raptis (Pablo) Santen de France et de Hollande, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Eritrea in Struggle: Association of Eritrean Students in North America, New York, NY, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Espirit: Espirit, Paris, France, 1952-1956 (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
- Etgar: Etgar, Israel, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Ethics and Policy: Center for Ethics and Social Policy, Berkeley, CA, circa 1980s (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Ethiopian Peoples' Revolutionary Party Program: Ethiopian People's Revolutionary Party/Ethiopian Students Union in North America, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Eulenspiegel: Eulenspiegel-Verlagsgesellschaft, Berlin, Germany, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Facts & Opinion: Chile Resource Center and Clearing House, San Francisco, CA, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Facts about the Palestine Problem: Arab Women's Information Committee, Beirut, Lebanon, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Falcemartello: La Varesina Grafica, Milan, Italy, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- fanal: Raul Nahrath, Koln, Germany, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10, Box 55, Folder 6)
- Faschismus oder Nationalsozialismus = Fascism or National Socialism, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Fateh: Palestine National Liberation Movement, Beirut, Lebanon / Montreal, Canada, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Festival: International Preparatory Committee for the VIIth World Festival of Youth and Students for Peace and Friendship, Vienna, Austria, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Fight Racism! Fight Imperialism!: Revolutionary Communist Group Publications, Watford, UK, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Focus on Jamaica: Focus on Jamaica Ltd., Montegro Bay, Jamaica, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Food First Backgrounder: Institute for Food and Development Policy, Oakland, CA, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Foreign Trade of the Democratic People's Republic of Korea: Foreign Trade Publishing House, Oesong District, Pyongyang, North Korea, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Fourth World: Masada, Downview, Ontario, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Franc-Tireur: Franc-Tireur, Paris, France, 1941 (Box Shared Tamiment 047, Folder 7)
- France Speaks!:, New York, NY, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Free Bulgaria: Free Bulgaria, Sofia, Bulgaria, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Free Economic Review: Shree Laxmi Narayan Press, Bombay, India, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Free Italy/L'Italia Libera: Italian People's Union, New York, NY, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Free Palestine: Friends of Free Palestine, Washington, DC, 1968-1973 (Box 38, Folder 11, Box 25, Folder 6-10)
- Frente Libertario: Frente Libertario, Paris, France, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 11, Box 38, Folder 7)
- Friends of Freedom: Friends of Freedom, Sooke, B.C., 1987 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Friends of Micronesia: Friends of Micronesia, Berkeley, CA, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6, Box 50)
- From Iran: Raha'i: Raha'i Translation Group, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Front Ouvrier: Front Ouvrier, Marseilles, France, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- FUPI's Answer to RIC: International Union of Students, Prague, Czechoslovakia, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Gazeta das Caldas: Gazeta das Caldas, Portugal, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- GDR Review: Verlag Zeit im Bild, Julian-Grimau-Allee, Dresden, Germany, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Germany Today Newsletter: The German American, Inc., New York, NY, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Gimtasis Krastas: Gimtasis Krastas, Vilnius, Lithuania, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Global Affairs: International Security Council, New York, NY, 1987-1990 (Box 50, Folder 7-12, Box 51, Folder 1-2)
- Global Exchanges: Global Exchange, San Francisco, CA, 1990-1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Guazapa: Centro de Ediciones Guazapa, El Salvador, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Guinea Gold: Port Moresby for Australians Fighting in New Guinea, Papua New Guinea, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Guyana News: Association of Concerned Guyanese-USA, Richmond Hill, NY, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Haiti Reborn: Quixote Center, Hyattsville, MD, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Haiti Support Network Update: Haiti Support Network, New York, NY, 1999-2000 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Haiti Sun: Republique d'Haiti, Port-au-Prince, Haiti, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- He...Basta!: He...Basta!, Quebec, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Hemisferica: Asociacion Interamericana Pro-Democracia y Libertad (AIDL), New York, NY, 1964-1979 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Iberica por la Libertad: Iberica Publishing Co., New York, NY, 1966-1973 (Box 51, Folder 4-10)
- Il Diverso: Sondalo, Italy, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Il Pensiero: dell'ateneo, Rome, Italy, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- In Struggle: Canadian Proletarian Party, Canada, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Inform: Redaktionskollektivet/Utomparlamentariska Motsandet i Storstockholm, Stockholm, Sweden, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Informador Guerrillero: Unidad Revolucionaria Macional Guatemalteca, Guatemala, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Information Bulletin: Coordinating Secretariat of National Unions of Students, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Information Bulletin: International Relations Department of the Central Committee of the Hungarian Working People's Party, Budapest, Hungary, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- informations dienst: organ der ikd fur innere information u. diskussion, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Informations Ouvrières: Informations Ouvrières, Paris, France, 1968-1985 (Box 27, Folder 10-18, Box 22, Folder 1-15, Box 39, Folder 1-16, Box 30, Box 29, Box 28, Box 41, Box 40, Box 44, Folder 1-6)
- Informe Colombiano: North American Network of Committees in Solidarity with Colombia, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Inside: Israel and the Occupied Arab Lands: ADC Research Institute, Washington, DC, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- International - A Survey of British and World Affairs: IMG Publications, London, UK, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- International Affairs Reports from Quaker Workers: American Friends Service Committee, Philadelphia, PA, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- International Affairs: A Monthly Journal of Political Analysis: All-Union Znaniye Society, Moscow, USSR, 1961-1986 (Box 8, Folder 1-5)
- International Background: NIFRA Publishers, Liechtenstein, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- International Living: William Bonner / Angora, Inc., Baltimore, MD, 1988-1992 (Box 52, Folder 1-7)
- International Newsletter: International Newsletter, Dublin, Ireland, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Internationalist Perspective: F. Destryker (editor), Staten Island, NY/Brussels, Belgium, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Internazionale: Rassegna, Rome, Italy, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Interrogations: Pour La Communaute Humaine: G. Byramjee, Paris, France, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Invariance: France, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Iran Liberation: Union of Moslem Iranian Students Societies Outside Iran, London, UK, 1982-1984 (Box 37, Folder 12, Box 23)
- ISC News: International Solidarity Committee, New York, NY, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
- ISRAC: Israeli Revolutionary Action Committee, London, UK, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Israel and Palestine Political Report: Magelan and Association Mashrek Development, Paris, France, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Israel Digest: Israel Office of Information, New York, NY, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Israel Press Briefs: International Center for Peace in the Middle East, Tel Aviv, Israel, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- IT: IT, London, UK, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Jahrbuch der National-Sozialistischen Wirtschaft: Munchner Buchgewerbehaus M. Muller & Sohn KG, Munich, Germany, 1937 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Jahrbuch fur Nationalsozialistische Wirtschaft: Verlag W. Kohlhammer, Stuttgart, Germany, 1935 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Jeruzalem: Jeruzalem, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Jeunesse du Monde: Federation Mondiale de la Jeunesse Democratique, Budapest, Hungary, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Josef-Städter Nachrichten: Josef-Stadter Nachrichten, Location unknown, 1935 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- KAFKA-Nieuwsbrief: KAFKA Brigade, Amsterdam, Netherlands, Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Kartell.NYTT: Kartell.NYTT, Oslo, Norway, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Ken: Ken, Inc., Chicago, IL, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Khmer Monthly News: Group of Khmer Residents in America, New York, NY, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Kleintje Muurkrant: Muurkantkollektief Den Bosch, Den Bosch, Netherlands, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 13-16, Box 37, Folder 6, Folder 13-14)
- Kleintje Muurkrant: Kleintje Murrkrant, Den Bosch, Netherlands, 1992-1993 (Box Shared Tamiment 051, Folder 12-13)
- L'Assiette au Beurre: L'Assiette au Beurre, Paris, France, 1934 (Box Shared Tamiment 047, Folder 3)
- L'Epoque: Paris, France, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- L'Hebdo Hara-Kiri: L'Hebdo Hara-Kiri, Paris, France, 1970 (Box Shared Tamiment 051, Folder 15)
- L'unique: E. Armand, Orleans, France, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- La Cause du Peuple: La Cause du Peuple, Paris, France, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- La Civilta Cattolica: Rome, Italy, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- La Hoja: Colectividad Los Arenalejos, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- La Idea Libre: Calle de Fernand el Catolico, Madrid, Spain, 1898 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- La Jeune Revolution: Organe de Liaison de la Jeuness Ouvriere et Intellectuelle, Paris, France, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- La Kritika Observanto: Paris, France, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- La Liberta: Economica Giostrelli, Perugia, Italy, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- La Lutte: La Lutte, Paris, France, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 8, Box 37)
- La Montagne: La Rievolution Sociale, France, 1871 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- La Mujer Indigena: Instituto Nacional de Antropologia e Historia, Mexico, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- La Nation: La Nation, France, 1892 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- La Nouvelle Critique (lanc.): L'union des Etudiants Communistes de France, Paris, France, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- La Parola: Italian Socialists Autonomous Federation, New York, NY, 1942-1944 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- La Pensee: Revue du Rationalisme Moderne: Editions Sociales Internationales, Paris, France, 1949-1953 (Box 10, Folder 1, Folder 13-14, Box 11, Folder 1-4, Box 12, Folder 1-2)
- La Protesta: Claudio Frollo, Madrid, Spain, 1901 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- La Releve: La Releve, Port-au-Prince, Haiti, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- La Revolution Proletarienne: Revolution Proletarienne, Paris, France, 1932-1950 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- La Revue M: Journal M, Paris, France, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- La Vanguardia: La Vanguardia, Barcelona, Spain, 1936-1938 (Box 23, Folder 18-19)
- La Verite: Organe du Comite Central de L'Organisation Communiste Internationaliste, Paris, France, 1971-1976 (Box 13, Folder 1-4, Box 54, Folder 3)
- La Voce: Degli Emigrati, Vive della Solidarieta Volontaria: Periodico Libertario in Germania: La Voce, Bochum, Germany, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Labour Candidate: Society of Labour Candidates, London, UK, 1941-1943 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Le Canard Enchaine: L'Oeuvre, Paris, France, 1934-1935 (Box Shared Tamiment 047, Folder 5)
- Le Frondeur: Le Frondeur, Paris, France, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Le Grand Illustre: Clermont-Ferrand, Paris, France, 1905 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Le Patriote: Le Patriote Enrg., Montreal, Quebec, 1936 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Le Semeur Contre Tous les Tyrants: Caennaise, Paris, France, 1928 (Box Shared Tamiment 047, Folder 4)
- Le Volontaire de la Liberte: International Brigades, Madrid, Spain, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Lebens-fragn: Lebens-fragn, Tel Aviv, Israel, 1965-1967 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Lecons D'une Dfaite: Lecons D'une Dfaite, Paris, France, Undated (Box 53, Folder 3)